CHARLIE PITKIN

741 Lakeside Dr Apt 309 Lincoln, NE 68528 308-870-1009

SUMMARY

I am a hardware system engineer, developer, and infrastructure admin for State Studios. Working for a startup requires me to think on the fly and come up with creative solutions to problems on a daily basis. It has been one of the best experiences that I have ever had and will never forget all I have learned and will continue to learn.

EXPERIENCE

STATE STUDIOS 04 / 2013 - Present

Hardware Systems Engineer

Myself and one other have been the only two full time employees since the founding of the company. We re-architected the main app from C# and SQL Server into a Node.js and MySQL based REST service. I have worked or built projects that involved Node.js, C++, Bash, Assembly, Raspberry Pi, Beagle Bone Black, OpenCV, LED panels, etc. We have also had to deal with the major issue of user and system security. We had to be mindful of these things while keeping our users in mind. I have deployed full service stacks including but not limited to MariaDB Galera cluster, MySQL, Zimbra SMTP, Postfix SMTP, Devcot, Roud Cude email client, Bugzilla, Pound Proxy, HAProxy, Burp Backup, and Node.js

XPANXION 04 / 2011 - 04 / 2013

Software Quality Assurance Analyst

- Manuel and Automated testing of web and mobile applications
- Testing includes unit, system, functional, ETL, and compatibility testing
- Worked with cross functional teams in agile-iterative and scrum development
- Test plan creation, test case development, QA lead experience
- Programs and platforms include- HP Quick Test Professional, HP Quality Center, iOS, Windows XP/7, Appian, and Fiddler

WEST PHARMACEUTICAL SERVICES

03 / 2010 - 04 / 2011

PC and Network Support Intern

Duties included: PC Support, Image deployment, Hardware upgrades and installs Technologies I have worked with include: Windows OS, Active Directory, VMware Server and Desktop, Microsoft Office, Symantec Ghost, PS Tools

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF NEBRASKA AT KEARNEY

2007 - 2011

Bachelors, Management Information Systems

Phi Beta Lambda, Association of Information Technology Professionals, Campus Activities Board

CERTIFICATIONS

CTFL

ISTQB